Guide to the Tyree Scott Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- COURT ORDER ADVISORY COMMITTEE RECORDS, 1965-1985; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 11/34-12/16)
  - Incoming Letters, 1970-1979; Subseries B (Box-folder 11/36-11/39-)
    - Incoming Letters, A-Z, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 11/39)
  - Outgoing Letters, 1971-1979; Subseries C (Box-folder 11/40-11/41-)
    - Outgoing Letters, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 11/40)
    - Outgoing Letters, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 11/41)
  - Intraorganizational Correspondence, 1970-1972; Subseries D (Box-folder 11/42)
    - Correspondence with United Construction Workers Association, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 11/42)
  - General Correspondence of Others, 1970-1978; Subseries E (Box-folder 11/43-11/44-)
    - United Construction Workers Association, 1978 (Box-folder 11/43)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 11/44)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 1970-1979; Subseries F (Box-folder 11/45-11/50)
    - Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 11/45)
    - MInutes, 1972 (Box-folder 11/46)
    - Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 11/47)
    - Minutes, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 11/48)
    - Subcommittees, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 11/49)
    - Minutes of Others, 1976 (Box-folder 11/50)
  - Financial Records, 1970-1978; Subseries G (Box-folder 11/51)
    - Financial Records, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 11/51)
  - Reports, 1970-1978; Subseries H (Box-folder 12/1-12/13)
    - Monthly Reports (Part 1 of 2), 1970-1973 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Monthly Reports (Part 2 of 2), 1970-1973 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Monthly Reports (Part 1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Monthly Reports (Part 2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Monthly Reports, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Monthly Reports, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Monthly Data Sheets, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Basic Data Sheets, 1978 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Accountant's Report: King-Snohomish Manpower Consortium, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Accountant's Report: King-Snohomish Manpower Consortium, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Reports from United Construction Workers Association, 1971 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Miscellaneous Reports, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Miscellaneous Reports, 1972 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Proposals and Agreements, 1972-1974; Subseries I (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Proposals and Agreements, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Lists, 1970-1978; Subseries J (Box-folder 12/15)
    - Lists, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965-1985; Subseries K (Box-folder 12/16)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1970s (Box-folder 12/16)
- UNITED INNER CITY DEVELOPMENT FOUNDATION RECORDS, 1971-1973; SERIES 3 (Box-folder 12/17-12/24)
  - Organizational Features, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Membership, 1973 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - General Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 12/20)
  - Speeches and Writings, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - Data Sheets on Other Organizations, 1971 (Box-folder 12/22)
  - Financial Records, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 12/23)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box-folder 12/24)
- SOUTHWEST WORKERS' FEDERATION RECORDS, 1965-1985; SERIES 4 (Box-folder 12/25-13/24)
  - Organizational Features, 1965-1985; Subseries A (Box-folder 12/25-12/28)
    - Organizational Features, 1973 (Box-folder 12/25)
    - Todd's Material, Organizational Material, 1973 (Box-folder 12/26)
    - Constitution, circa 1970s (Box-folder 12/27)
    - UCWA Southern Works, 1973 (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 1974-1977; Subseries B (Box-folder 12/29-12/30)
    - Quarterly Advisory Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 12/29)
    - Minutes, 1977 (Box-folder 12/30)
  - Speeches and Writings, 1975-1975; Subseries C (Box-folder 12/31)
    - Speeches and Writings, 1975 (Box-folder 12/31)
  - Proposals, 1973-1976; Subseries D (Box-folder 12/32)
    - Proposals, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 12/32)
  - Newsletters, 1976-1976; Subseries E (Box-folder 12/33)
    - Newsletters, 1976 (Box-folder 12/33)
  - Event Files: Dallas Meetings, 1965-1985; Subseries F (Box-folder 12/34-13/9)
    - Dallas Meetings, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 12/34)
    - Meeting Material, 1973 (Box-folder 12/35)
    - Dallas II, circa 1970s (Box-folder 12/36)
    - Video Tape Dallas I and II, circa 1970s (Box-folder 12/37)
    - Dallas II Meeting Agenda, Info, Memos, 1973 (Box-folder 12/38)
    - Dallas Transportation, 1973 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Bishop College: Meeting Logistics, 1973 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Dallas I, 1973 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Dallas II, 1973 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Dallas II: Budget, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Dallas II, 1973 (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Dallas Meeting, 1973 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Dallas II Meeting Material, 1973 (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Trade Union Conference Dallas, 1977 (Box-folder 13/9)
  - City Files, 1965-1985; Subseries G (Box-folder 13/10-13/23)
    - Austin, Texas, circa 1970s (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Monroe, Louisiana, 1973 (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1973 (Box-folder 13/14)
    - Pine Bluff, Arkansas, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 13/15)
    - Pine Bluff, Arkansas, 1973 (Box-folder 13/16)
    - Shreveport, Louisiana, 1973 (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Shreveport, Louisiana, 1973 (Box-folder 13/18)
    - Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1974 (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Tyler, Texas, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 13/21)
    - Tyler, Texas, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 13/22)
    - Wasco, Texas, 1973 (Box-folder 13/23)
  - Subject Files, 1975-1976; Subseries H (Box-folder 13/24)
    - Wages, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 13/24)
- ALASKA CANNERY WORKERS ASSOCIATION RECORDS, 1973-1976; SERIES 5 (Box-folder 13/25-13/27)
  - Meeting Materials, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 13/25)
  - Correspondence, Meeting Materials, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 13/26)
  - Correspondence and Resources, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 13/27)
- ORGANIZING COMMITTEE FOR AN IDEOLOGICAL CENTER RECORDS, 1965-1985; SERIES 6 (Box-folder 13/28-15/11)
  - Organizational Records, 1965-1985; Subseries A (Box-folder 13/28-14/9)
    - Organizational Features, 1965-1985; Part 1 (Box-folder 13/28-13/42)
      - Funding Statement, circa 1970s (Box-folder 13/28)
      - Principles of Unity, circa 1970s (Box-folder 13/29)
      - Minutes, 1978 (Box-folder 13/30)
      - Guidelines for Investigation of Trend Individuals and Organizations, 1978 (Box-folder 13/31)
      - Draft Resolution for Ideological Center, circa 1970s (Box-folder 13/32)
      - Funding Meeting Minutes, 1978 (Box-folder 13/33)
      - Statement on Racism, 1978 (Box-folder 13/34)
      - Speeches and Writings, circa 1970s (Box-folder 13/35)
      - Statements, 1980 (Box-folder 13/36)
      - Speeches and Writings, 1980 (Box-folder 13/37)
      - Speeches and Writings, circa 1970s (Box-folder 13/38)
      - Notes, circa 1970s (Box-folder 13/39)
      - Lists, Available Members, circa 1970s (Box-folder 13/40)
      - Mailing Lists, 1978 (Box-folder 13/41)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box-folder 13/42)
    - Subject Files, 1965-1985; Part 2 (Box-folder 13/43-14/9)
      - Buffalo Workers Movement, 1978 (Box-folder 13/43)
      - Cadre Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 13/44)
      - Collapse of OCIC, 1981 (Box-folder 13/45)
      - Collapse of OCIC, 1981 (Box-folder 13/46)
      - Criticism/Self Criticism, circa 1970s (Box-folder 13/47)
      - Responses to Five Questions, 1977 (Box-folder 13/48)
      - G-4, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 13/49)
      - Local Center, 1979 (Box-folder 13/50)
      - Local Centers, 1980 (Box-folder 13/51)
      - Local Center Proposals, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 13/52)
      - Milwaukee Conference, 1980 (Box-folder 13/53)
      - Milwaukee Conference, 1980 (Box-folder 13/54)
      - Milwaukee Conference, 1980 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Milwaukee Conference, 1980 (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Party Building Meeting Atlanta, 1978 (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Party Building Conference Baltimore, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Party Building (Organization Members Only), 1978 (Box-folder 14/5)
      - Point 18 Conference, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 14/6)
      - Portland Waterway Terminal, 1979 (Box-folder 14/7)
      - Regional Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Western Regional Conference on Draft Plan, 1980 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Committee Records, 1965-1985; Subseries B (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Various Committees, 1965-1985; Part 1 (Box-folder 14/10-14/29)
      - Material from the Committee of Five, 1978 (Box-folder 14/10)
      - Bay Area Workers' Organizing Committee (1 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 14/11)
      - Bay Area Workers' Organizing Committee (2 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 14/12)
      - Education Committee, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 14/13)
      - Steering Committee, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 14/14)
      - Boc, 1978 (Box-folder 14/15)
      - El Comite - Movimiento De Izquierda Nacional Puertorriqueño (Movement of the Puerto Rican National Left), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 14/16)
      - Guardian Club Networks, 1979 (Box-folder 14/17)
      - Guardian Club Network, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 14/18)
      - Los Angeles Workers Group, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 14/19)
      - Milwaukee Alliance, 1978 (Box-folder 14/20)
      - National Network of Marxist-Leninist Clubs, 1979 (Box-folder 14/21)
      - Pasadena Community Information Center, circa 1970s (Box-folder 14/22)
      - Philadelphia Workers Organizing Committee In-Correspondence, 1978 (Box-folder 14/23)
      - Philadelphia Workers Organizing Committee, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 14/24)
      - Incoming Correspondence, circa 1970s (Box-folder 14/25)
      - Study Program Philadelphia Workers Organizing Committee, circa 1970s (Box-folder 14/26)
      - Philadelphia Workers Organizing Committee: Trade Union Conference Philadelphia, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 14/27)
      - Philadelphia Workers Organizing Committee: Racism, 1980 (Box-folder 14/28)
      - Philadelphia Workers Organizing Committee: Miscellaneous, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 14/29)
    - Seattle Workers Group, 1965-1985; Part 2 (Box-folder 14/30-15/11)
      - History, circa 1970s (Box-folder 14/30)
      - Rules, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 14/31)
      - Incoming Letters, 1979 (Box-folder 14/32)
      - Outgoing Letters, 1978 (Box-folder 14/33)
      - Early Planning Meeting, 1976 (Box-folder 14/34)
      - Evaluation Question and Answer, circa 1970s (Box-folder 14/35)
      - Research Material Seattle, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 14/36)
      - Subject Files: Class Analysis, circa 1970s (Box-folder 14/37)
      - Subject Files: Criticism/Self-Criticism, circa 1970s (Box-folder 14/38)
      - Subject Files: Criticism/Self-Criticism, 1978 (Box-folder 14/39)
      - Subject Files: Forum with Guardian Club, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 14/40)
      - Subject Files: Marxist-Leninist Education Project, 1979 (Box-folder 14/41)
      - Subject Files: Notes on Organization, circa 1970s (Box-folder 15/1)
      - Subject Files: Study Notes on Political Education, circa 1970s (Box-folder 15/2)
      - Subject Files: Study Materials, circa 1970s (Box-folder 15/3)
      - Subject Files: Study Practice Meeting, 1977 (Box-folder 15/4)
      - Subject Files: Trade Union, circa 1970s (Box-folder 15/5)
      - Subject Files: United Construction Workers Association PWD Meeting Notes, 1976 (Box-folder 15/6)
      - Subject Files: Workplace Investigation, circa 1970s (Box-folder 15/7)
      - Subject Files: Workers Party Notes, circa 1970s (Box-folder 15/8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box-folder 15/9)
      - Miscellaneous, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 15/10)
      - Socialist Organizing Committee, 1978 (Box-folder 15/11)
- AMERICAN FRIENDS SERVICE COMMITTEE, PACIFIC NORTHWEST REGIONAL OFFICE RECORDS, 1965-1990; SERIES 7 (Box-folder 15/12-16/8)
  - Organizational Information, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Outgoing Letters, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 15/13)
  - Intraorganizational Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 15/14)
  - Intraorganizational Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 15/15)
  - Intraorganizational Correspondence, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 15/16)
  - Minutes, 1973, 1988-1979 (Box-folder 15/17)
  - Financial Records, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 15/18)
  - Speeches and Writings, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 15/19)
  - Proposals, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 15/20)
  - Reports, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 15/21)
  - Releases, 1973 (Box-folder 15/22)
  - Job Descriptions, 1979, 1987, 1990 (Box-folder 15/23)
  - Publications, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 15/24)
  - Subject Files: Angola, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 15/25)
  - Subject Files: Atlanta Meeting, LELO and Other, 1973 (Box-folder 15/26)
  - Subject Files: Cummins Engine Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 15/27)
  - Subject Files: Community Relations/Justice S-1, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 15/28)
  - Subject Files: Dallas Travel Information, 1973 (Box-folder 15/29)
  - Subject Files: Gay/Lesbian Program, 1988 (Box-folder 15/30)
  - Subject Files: Olongopo Film, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 15/31)
  - Subject Files: Women's Conference, 1978 (Box-folder 15/32)
  - Subject Files: Contacts from Women's Conference, 1978 (Box-folder 15/33)
  - Subject Files: Women's Program, 1977 (Box-folder 15/34)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 15/35)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box-folder 15/36)
  - Affirmative Action Committee Records, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 15/37)
  - Third World Coalition: Organizational Information, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 15/38)
  - Third World Coalition: Incoming Letters, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 15/39)
  - Third World Coalition: Outgoing Letters, 1976 (Box-folder 15/40)
  - Third World Coalition: Intraorganizational Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 15/41)
  - Third World Coalition: Minutes and Agenda, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 15/42)
  - Third World Coalition: Speeches and Writings, 1976 (Box-folder 15/43)
  - Third World Coalition: Reports, 1976 (Box-folder 15/44)
  - Third World Coalition: Proposals, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 15/45)
  - Third World Coalition: Newsletters, 1977 (Box-folder 15/46)
  - Third World Coalition - Subject Files: People's Republic of China, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 15/47)
  - Third World Coalition - Subject Files: Philadelphia, 1976 (Box-folder 15/48)
  - Third World Coalition - Subject Files: Newsletter Material, 1974 (Box-folder 15/49)
  - Third World Coalition - Subject Files: Philadelphia, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Third World Coalition - Subject Files: Review, 1976 (Box-folder 16/2)
  - Third World Coalition - Notes and Ephemera, circa 1970s (Box-folder 16/3)
  - Third World Coalition - Labor Task Force Conference, 1977 (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Third World Coalition - Labor Task Force, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Third World Coalition - Women's Task Force, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Third World Coalition - Women's Task Force, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Third World Coalition - Labor, 1977 (Box-folder 16/8)
- TYREE SCOTT PERSONAL PAPERS, 1965-1984; SERIES 8 (Box-folder 16/9-16/29)
  - Incoming Letters, 1978 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Financial Records, Farwest Insurance Receipts, 1978 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Appointment Books (1 of 2), 1975-1978 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Appointment Books (2 of 2), 1975-1978 (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Address Books, circa 1970s (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Notes (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 16/14)
  - Notes (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 16/15)
  - Notes, 1984 (Box-folder 16/16)
  - Notes, circa 1980s (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Notes, circa 1980s (Box-folder 16/18)
  - Subject Series: Housing Lots, 1979 (Box-folder 16/19)
  - Subject Series: National Lawyers Guild, 1976 (Box-folder 16/20)
  - Subject Series: Redlining, 1976 (Box-folder 16/21)
  - Subject Series: Southern Africa, 1977 (Box-folder 16/22)
  - Subject Series: Communist Newsletters, circa 1930s (Box-folder 16/23)
  - Subject Series: Southern Africa Position Papers, 1995 (Box-folder 16/24)
  - Cards, circa 1980s (Box-folder 16/25)
  - Ephemera: Photos, circa 1970s (Box-folder 16/26)
  - Ephemera, circa 1970s (Box-folder 16/27)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 16/28)
  - Miscellaneous: Passport Forms, circa 1970s (Box-folder 16/29)
- MICHAEL D. WOO PAPERS, 1965-1985; SERIES 9 (Box-folder 16/30-16/31)
  - Financial Records, circa 1970s (Box-folder 16/30)
  - Financial Records: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 16/31)
- NORTHWEST LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE (LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE) RECORDS, 1961-2005; SERIES 10 (Box-folder 16/32-45/15)
  - Organizational Records, 1965-1994; Subseries A (Box-folder 16/32-17/21)
    - General Correspondence, 1972-1990; Part 1 (Box-folder 16/32-16/41)
      - Ford Foundation, 1974 (Box-folder 16/32)
      - Gibbs, Douglas, Theiler, and Yarshefsky re: Loan, 1980 (Box-folder 16/33)
      - John Hay Whitney Foundation, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 16/34)
      - Northwest Chicano Radio Network, 1989 (Box-folder 16/35)
      - Public Welfare Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 16/36)
      - United Farm Workers Service Center, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 16/37)
      - United States Internal Revenue Service, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 16/38)
      - Warsh, Herman (the Youth Project), 1979-1981 (Box-folder 16/39)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973, 1987-1977, 1990 (Box-folder 16/40)
      - Organizational and Historical Features, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 16/41)
    - Minutes and Agenda, 1973-1990; Part 2 (Box-folder 16/42-16/44)
      - Board of Directors Meeting, 1973-1990 (Box-folder 16/42)
      - Executive Committee Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 16/43)
      - Staff Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 16/44)
    - Subject Files, 1965-1991; Part 3 (Box-folder 16/45-17/12)
      - "A Dry White Season" Film Screening, 1989 (Box-folder 16/45)
      - Alternative Trade Organizations, 1988 (Box-folder 16/46)
      - Comite De Apoyo A Los Trabajadores Agricolas (CATA), 1989-1990 (Box-folder 16/47)
      - Committee for Economic Opportunity re: Port of Seattle, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 16/48)
      - Committee for Economic Opportunity re: Port of Seattle, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 16/49)
      - Community Forum on Malcolm X, 1990 (Box-folder 16/50)
      - Divestment of Seattle City Employees' Pension Fund, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 16/51)
      - Domingo Viernes Jefferson Fund, 1987 (Box-folder 16/52)
      - Justice for Janitors, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 17/1)
      - Labor and Employment Law Office Work regarding Cuba, 1990 (Box-folder 17/2)
      - Oregon Reforestation Cooperative, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 17/3)
      - Planning for Progressive Agendas Conference, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 17/4)
      - Port of Seattle regarding South Africa, 1989 (Box-folder 17/5)
      - Puget Sound Conversion Project Sub-Lease, 1980 (Box-folder 17/6)
      - Seafood Workers Educational and Economic Project (SWEEP), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 17/7)
      - Title VII Project, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 17/8)
      - Udall, Morris, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 17/9)
      - United States Department of Labor Bid Conditions, circa 1970s (Box-folder 17/10)
      - Washington Association for Community Economic Development, 1989 (Box-folder 17/11)
      - Washington State Department of Labor and Industries' Proposal regarding Children and Farm Labor, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Speeches and Writings, 1965-1985; Part 4 (Box-folder 17/13)
      - Speeches and Writings, circa 1970s (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Financial Records, 1974-1990; Part 5 (Box-folder 17/14)
      - Financial Records, 1974, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Ordinance, 1989; Part 6 (Box-folder 17/15)
      - City of Seattle Amendment of Women's and Minority Utilization, 1989 (Box-folder 17/15)
    - Court Papers, 1973; Part 7 (Box-folder 17/16)
      - Stamps vs. Detroit Edison, 1973 (Box-folder 17/16)
    - Cassette Tapes, 1994; Part 8 (Box-folder 17/17-17/18)
      - Campfire House and Employment Coalition, 1994 (Box-folder 17/17)
      - Rami Dictation re: Migrant Seasonal Labor Force and Minority Workers in Canneries (discrimination), undated (Box-folder 17/18)
    - Notes, Undated; Part 9 (Box-folder 17/19-17/20)
      - Notes, undated (Box-folder 17/19)
      - Notes, undated (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Miscellany, 1977, 1989; Part 10 (Box-folder 17/21)
      - Miscellany, 1977, 1989 (Box-folder 17/21)
  - Mozambique, 1973-2005; Subseries B (Box-folder 17/22-)
    - Historical Features, Undated; Part 1 (Box-folder 17/22)
      - Historical Features, undated (Box-folder 17/22)
    - General Correspondence, 1988-1995; Part 2 (Box-folder 17/23-17/26)
      - Cashews, Official Documents, Etc., 1988-1990 (Box-folder 17/23)
      - R.J. Hyslop and Associates, 1991 (Box-folder 17/24)
      - Tyree in Mozambique, 1991 (Box-folder 17/25)
      - Miscellaneous, 1988, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 17/26)
    - Project Files, 1985-2005; Part 3 (Box-folder 17/27-18/6)
      - African/Northwest Construction Exchange, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 17/27)
      - Art Project, 1988 (Box-folder 17/28)
      - Cashew Project (Market Info), 1989-1990 (Box-folder 17/29)
      - Cashew Project (Meetings), 1987-1990 (Box-folder 17/30)
      - Cashew Project (Sales), 1989-1991 (Box-folder 17/31)
      - Citrus, 1991 (Box-folder 17/32)
      - Fishing Plan, undated (Box-folder 17/33)
      - Housing Rehabilitation in Maputo, undated (Box-folder 17/34)
      - Medical Equipment Donation, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 17/35)
      - Mozambican Relief, 1988 (Box-folder 17/36)
      - Rehabilitation of Umbeluzi Production Center, circa 1990s (Box-folder 17/37)
      - Seafood, 1991 (Box-folder 17/38)
      - Seeds, 1991 (Box-folder 17/39)
      - Tazama Visit, 1990 (Box-folder 18/1)
      - Timber, 1990 (Box-folder 18/2)
      - Timber, 1990 (Box-folder 18/3)
      - Timber, 1990 (Box-folder 18/4)
      - Travel to Mozambique, 1988 (Box-folder 18/5)
      - Miscellaneous Projects, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Subject Series, 1984-1994; Part 4 (Box-folder 18/7-18/19)
      - Election Monitoring, 1994 (Box-folder 18/7)
      - Establishment of Mozambique Projects, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 18/8)
      - Flight Delivery, 1991 (Box-folder 18/9)
      - Glocomo Church Investors, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 18/10)
      - Material and Shipment Guidelines, 1988 (Box-folder 18/11)
      - Mozambique, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 18/12)
      - Nealy, Marc, undated (Box-folder 18/13)
      - Press Conference regarding: Missionaries/Renamo, 1989 (Box-folder 18/14)
      - Shipping, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18/15)
      - Soderquist, Steve, 1991 (Box-folder 18/16)
      - White, Tony, 1990 (Box-folder 18/17)
      - Tyree in Mozambique, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 18/18)
      - Wood Processing Facility, 1990 (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Publications, 1989-1990; Part 5 (Box-folder 18/20)
      - Revista Fiscal and Tempo, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18/20)
    - Photographs, Undated; Part 6 (Box-folder 18/21-18/22)
      - Photographs, undated (Box-folder 18/21)
      - Photographs, undated (Box-folder 18/22)
    - Notes, 1985-2005; Part 7 (Box-folder 18/23)
      - Tyree's Work in Mozambique, circa 1990s (Box-folder 18/23)
    - Miscellany, 1983-1994; Part 8 (Box-folder 18/24-18/25)
      - Miscellany, 1992 (Box-folder 18/24)
      - Miscellany, 1983, 1990, 1994 (Box-folder 18/25)
    - Puget Sound Development Foundation, 1989-1990; Part 9 (Box-folder 18/26-18/29)
      - Puget Sound Development Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18/26)
      - Puget Sound Development Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18/27)
      - Puget Sound Development Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18/28)
      - Puget Sound Development Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18/29)
    - Legal Services Center, 1973-1974; Part 10 (Box-folder 18/30-18/32)
      - Legal Services Center, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 18/30)
      - Legal Services Center, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 18/31)
      - Legal Services Center, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 18/32)
  - Case Files and Legal Papers, 1961-1995; Subseries C (Box-folder 18/33-45/15)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: General Correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 18/33)